<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517000000 +0000" stop="20240517003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Sermon For Today</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A visiting preacher gives a sermon about taking time to relax. In trying to create an atmosphere of relaxation on a Sunday afternoon, the townsfolk all end up running themselves ragged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517003000 +0000" stop="20240517010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Briscoe Declares For Aunt Bee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Briscoe Darling becomes obsessed with Aunt Bee after hearing her recite a poem, going as far as to kidnap her and bring her back to his shack in the hills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517010000 +0000" stop="20240517013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Clampett's Millions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is still working on being a 007 spy, though it is annoying Granny. And Elly has been crowned Queen of the Bankers Ball. Mr. Cushing is not happy about this though, as he wanted his contestant to win. Because Jethro is having more fun at Cushing’s bank, he tries to get Jed to transfer his money to the Merchant’s Bank. And Cushing sees this opportunity and tries to get that gorgeous Clampett account.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517013000 +0000" stop="20240517020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>A Prize In Every Package</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Criminals rob a jewelry store in Chicago and stash their haul in a grain bin. The expensive gems end up packed in boxes of Crickly Wickly cereal shipped to Hooterville. Lisa knows real jewels when she sees them, but Oliver's sure they're just costume. After taking them to be appraised, the sheriff arrests Oliver for the jewelry store heist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517020000 +0000" stop="20240517023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink For The Defense</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink is appointed defense counsel for a German officer on trial for treason who has secret plans intended for London. Hogan helps Klink prove the officer's innocence in order to secure the plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517023000 +0000" stop="20240517030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Kamikazes Are Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys find a new rocket that has landed near camp. They are at a loss on how to get it back to England for study when Marya and her rocket-designing husband enter camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517030000 +0000" stop="20240517033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Roddy Mcdowall</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mrs. Wiggins, Carol plays a flighty secretary who can't use a door buzzer correctly. Then, in Medical Documentary, a starry-eyed doctor uses his patient to get famous. Finally, in The Lift, Carol reunites with an old flame in a series of one-word exchanges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517033000 +0000" stop="20240517043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Renegade Refugee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A journalist is murdered while tracking an ex-Nazi war criminal who may be posing as an executive at a company called Space Associates, Ltd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517043500 +0000" stop="20240517050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Denton On Doomsday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A has-been, drunk gunslinger finds his fast-draw abilities magically restored.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517050500 +0000" stop="20240517053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Invitation To An Accident</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A man tries to tell another man that his wife is cheating on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517053500 +0000" stop="20240517060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Arthur</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A chicken farmer murders his gold-digging girlfriend but the police can't convict him without the body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517060500 +0000" stop="20240517070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Death Has No Face</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix's search for the source of a death threat takes him to a small town. Shortly after he arrives, he's framed for murder and imprisoned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517070500 +0000" stop="20240517080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Exchange</sub-title>
    <desc>Private eyes so rarely get a vacation free of peril, and Cannon is no exception. He goes fishing, little knowing that someone from his police past is hunting him: a murderer determined on revenge for the time he spent in prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517080500 +0000" stop="20240517090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>School Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Drug dealers infiltrate a treatment center and murder J.R.'s counselor friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517090000 +0000" stop="20240517093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Drug dealers murder a roadside diner owner for his location.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517093000 +0000" stop="20240517100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Amateur Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Citizens are full of praise for Officer Gideon C. Dengle, wanting to bestow him with awards, honors and home-baked cookies. There's only one problem: there's no such officer in the LAPD.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517100000 +0000" stop="20240517103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Starlet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage runaway, intent on becoming a star, has instead wound up in pornographic films. Acting on behalf of the girl's aunt, Friday and Gannon try to find the young "starlet."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517103000 +0000" stop="20240517110000 +0000">
    <title>My Three Sons</title>
    <sub-title>One By One They Go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Chip and Polly return from their honeymoon, and Chip faces a father-in-law who refuses to speak to his newly married daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517110000 +0000" stop="20240517120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Yachts Rock</sub-title>
    <desc>"All aboard Bill's new boat, "Toast to Coast"!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517120000 +0000" stop="20240517123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Bad Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>An incident at the park leads to Beaver ripping the pants on his gray flannel suit. When he's questioned by Ward and June he makes up a wild story that his parents quickly see through. Lectured in telling the truth, Beaver does just that when the pants of his other suit are ripped but Ward and June don't believe him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517123000 +0000" stop="20240517130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Boarding School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Wally's stops by with stories about how great it is at the military school he attends. This leads Wally to decide that he would like to attend military school, despite a wary Ward and June.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517130000 +0000" stop="20240517140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Traveling Treasure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>His fishing trip ruined, Mason is on the case when a deep-sea fisherman aboard a rented boat is found dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517140000 +0000" stop="20240517150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It appears that a ghost has hired Matlock when the attorney learns the man who hired him to defend his wife is in fact the man she is accused of murdering!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517150000 +0000" stop="20240517160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Brother's Keeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Louann's ne'er-do-well brother returns home after being paroled.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517160000 +0000" stop="20240517170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Roots</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An itinerant worker and his young son stay with the Waltons, causing the son to want his father to give up life on the road</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517170000 +0000" stop="20240517180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Reward</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A convicted gold-mine swindler gets out of prison to resume mining—with money he's accused of stealing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517180000 +0000" stop="20240517190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Second Sight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E16</episode-num>
    <desc>When Jamie goes missing, the Cartwrights enlist the help of a reluctant clairvoyant to locate the youngster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517190000 +0000" stop="20240517193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Old Tony</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and his girlfriend, Laurie, discover that an old hermit is very lonely.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517193000 +0000" stop="20240517200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sharpshooter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas McCain and his son, Mark, arrive in North Fork, New Mexico. Looking to start a new life, they come across a ranch that is to their liking, which is for sale. Lucas enters a Turkey Shoot in hopes of winning the down payment for the ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517200000 +0000" stop="20240517210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Brian Conlin Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>"Brian Conlin walks into Hale's camp, delirious and dehydrated. After he recovers, he leads Coop to his group of Irish immigrants, whose wagons have broken down, and Hale invites them to join the wagon train. However, having been repeatedly turned away from place after place, most members of Conlin's group are slow to trust anyone or accept help."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517210000 +0000" stop="20240517213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 14 -- S.w.a.t.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are the first to respond to a downtown rooftop sniper who has been indiscriminately shooting at anyone he can find with his scoped rifle. After risking their lives to get civilians out of his line of sight, they become lead participants in the S.W.A.T. team's attempt to neutralize the suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517213000 +0000" stop="20240517220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 64 -- Bottom Of The Bottle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed see the same drunk twice in one night, respond to a bar fight and engage in a high-speed pursuit with good samaritans who make a bad decision. They also search for a biker who tries to coerce a woman to repay a debt by riddling her apartment with buckshot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517220000 +0000" stop="20240517223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>They Call The Wind Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A strong windstorm affects the M*A*S*H personnel in varying ways: Hawkeye and most of the unit busy themselves securing items that could blow away; Radar prepares his animal hutch for the worst; a disgusted Charles switches his Tokyo-leave transportation from air to ground and runs into a difficult medical situation en route to Seoul.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517223000 +0000" stop="20240517230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Ego</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Tom Greenleigh of "Stars and Stripes" comes to the 4077th to write an article about Charles, which makes him act even more egotistical than usual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517230000 +0000" stop="20240517233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Baby, It's Cold Outside</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>While everyone is complaining about the record cold snap, Charles becomes the most unpopular man in camp, when his parents send him a winterized polar suit that he insists on flaunting in front of everyone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240517233000 +0000" stop="20240518000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Point Of View</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In this unique episode, the camera becomes the eyes of a young wounded soldier. It records his sensory responses to being wounded, flown by helicopter to the 4077th, examined, operated on and treated in post-operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518000000 +0000" stop="20240518003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer The House Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy takes Gomer in after Wally fires him for not doing his job right. Gomer proceeds to drive Andy, Aunt Bee and Opie crazy with all of the noise he makes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518003000 +0000" stop="20240518010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Black Day For Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are to protect a shipment of gold passing through Mayberry. It's critical that they keep it a secret, but Barney spills the beans immediately and soon all the town knows.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518010000 +0000" stop="20240518013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Drysdale's Dog Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny demands to see her money in cash, and Drysdale tries to talk her out of it. He fails and upsets the Clampetts by accidentally throwing magazines at them, which were really aimed at his wife and her dog. He tries to make things better by showing Granny what a million dollars looks like to turn her off from the idea, but ends up throwing more stuff at her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518013000 +0000" stop="20240518020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Law Partners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Recent law school graduate Brian Williams pitches Oliver on joining him in a new practice. After another of his patriotic speeches, this time about law, Oliver is ready to hang out his shingle. Meanwhile, Lisa is excited about becoming their secretary and Eb is ready to run the farm.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518020000 +0000" stop="20240518023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Kommandant Gertrude</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must get a U.S. general out of Stalag 13, while Klink plans to move the camp's fence line and Gertrude arrives with her fiancé.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518023000 +0000" stop="20240518030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan's Double Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hogan is identified as a saboteur, he impersonates a German officer in front of the very Gestapo agent who could take him down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518030000 +0000" stop="20240518033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Whiplash / Family, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In Whiplash, Harvey fakes an injury to scam an unsuspecting Carol. Then, in The Family, Eunice and Mama are mad after they attend the anniversary of her husband's co-worker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518033000 +0000" stop="20240518043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Unwelcome Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy Walter Frazer has always blamed his daughter-in-law, Sue Ellen, for the failures of his son, Gregson. You can only imagine how he feels when Sue Ellen is accused of Gregson's murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518043500 +0000" stop="20240518050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Sixteen-millimeter Shrine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An aging former movie star lives and dreams in the past, constantly watching her old movies alone in isolation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518050500 +0000" stop="20240518053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Crystal Trench</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman heads for the mountain in Switzerland on which her husband died while climbing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518053500 +0000" stop="20240518060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Appointment At Eleven</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>An angry young man accurately predicts an impending death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518060500 +0000" stop="20240518070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Small Favor For An Old Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix loses a friend, a small time mob courier killed flying money to Mexico. The mobsters, certain Mannix stole their loot, come after the detective with a vengeance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518070500 +0000" stop="20240518080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Game Children Play</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is hired when the only witness to a robbery is a young child who blames an Arabian heir for the crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518080500 +0000" stop="20240518090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Cry For Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-policeman, whose son was killed as a warning not to interfere with the local protection racket, leads a vigilante group in a barrio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518090000 +0000" stop="20240518093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Cannonball, Inc.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After a derailment, Hooterville residents take over operation of the Cannonball from Homer Bedloe, and demand so many changes that the train's crew decides to quit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518093000 +0000" stop="20240518100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Kate Grounds Selma Plout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Kate Bradley tangles with Selma Plout when Selma tries to lure pilot Steve Elliott into marriage with her daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518100000 +0000" stop="20240518103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Badger Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A young girl shows up at the Clampett mansion, claiming she is a friend from back home, Emaline Fetty. The Clampetts welcome her into their house. But it turns out that Emaline is working with someone to blackmail the Clampetts. She takes pictures of her and Jed in a compromising position. Colonel Foxhall, the man who is in control of the caper, and Emaline develop the photos and show them to Jane and Drysdale, who believe something else is going on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518103000 +0000" stop="20240518110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Badgers Return</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale is intent on getting the Clampetts to identify Colonel Foxhall and Emaline Fetty as dangerous criminals. Emaline is in hiding, but visits Jethro, tricking him into helping her hide from the police. The Clampetts mistake the officer that brought Foxhall as a criminal, and Foxhall gets away from the man holding him and hides in the Clampett mansion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518110000 +0000" stop="20240518113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Quiet! Pleeze, Popeye Meets William Tell, Nearlyweds, Matinee Idol Popeye</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye starts a one-man anti-noise campaign when his Pappy suffers that "morning-after" feeling and street sounds aggravate it., Popeye has need of his spinach when he poses as William Tell's son for the big apple-shooting contest, especially when he finds that the old man's aim isn't what it used to be!, Popeye and Bluto both plan to marry Olive Oyl., Brutus is an egotistical French director making a film about Antony and Cleopatra, starring Popeye and Olive Oyl."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518113000 +0000" stop="20240518120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Trap Happy, Screwball Squirrel, Pecos Pest</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom hires an exterminator, another cat, to get rid of Jerry., Screwy Squirrel abuses Meathead dog with numerous gags until the dog has finally had enough and begs for the cartoon to end., Jerry's Uncle Pecos keeps having his guitar strings snapped so Tom keeps losing his whiskers to replace them."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518120000 +0000" stop="20240518130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Saddle-sore Woody, Lighthouse Keeping Blues, Coy Decoy, Cool It Charlie, Wild Bill Hiccup, Space Mouse, The Tenant's Racket</sub-title>
    <desc>"Dirty McNasty kipnaps Sugarfoot, and Woody follows him into town to get him back., Chilly breaks the bright light bulbs of a lighthouse that are keeping him awake. But lighthouse keeper Smedley keeps replacing them., Woody uses a hunter's own decoy ducks to confuse and hurt his hunting dog., Charlie attempts to install an air conditioner himself to save money., Wild Bill Hiccup chases Woody and Sugarfoot around a haunted house., Doc tries to capture and sell Hickory and Dickory as lab mice to NASA., Woody moves into a birdhouse and kicks the bird homeowner out. The human owner of the main house tries to get rid of Woody for the bird."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518130000 +0000" stop="20240518140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Napoleon Bunny-part, Run, Run Sweet Road Runner (1965), The Shell Shocked Egg, The Fair Haired Hare, Really Scent, Mother Was A Rooster, A Star Is Bored</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs goes back in time and meets Napoleon who he annoys so much that he sends his guards to arrest Bugs., Wile E. Coyote attempts numerous ways to catch the Road Runner.
, A mother turtle buries her eggs in the sand. While she is away, one of the eggs partly hatches and begins roaming the countryside trying to finish hatching.
, A fight breaks out over property when Yosemite Sam builds his house over Bug Bunny's underground house. A judge rules that they must share it until one of them shall pass on. Thus begins Sam's attempts to out the rabbit.
, Pepe falls in love with a cat with a white stripe.
, The barnyard dog steals an ostrich egg and places it by Foggy. When Foggy wakes up, he thinks he has laid a huge egg
, Daffy Duck is jealous of Bugs Bunny's stardom. He demands to be put into a film and lands a role as Bugs' stunt double.
"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518140000 +0000" stop="20240518150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Winged Terror (1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After a series of disturbing incidents involving a raven that seems to hypnotize high-ranking officials into committing dastardly deeds, Agents West and Harper decide to find out what's going on. The incidents lead the new partners to a group calling themselves The Raven, led by Thaddeus Toombs and a man called Tycho (who has an enormous head and is very smart).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518150000 +0000" stop="20240518160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Alice Whitetree Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>"Coop falls for a young half-Indian woman wandering alone in the wilderness. He brings her to the wagon train, where Hale discovers she is a survivor of a tribe totally massacred ten years earlier. A sheriff says she has killed two people."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518160000 +0000" stop="20240518170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Profit And The Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Heath saves the life of a hired killer who is on the way to stockton to kill—Heath.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518170000 +0000" stop="20240518180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Malachi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Town drunk Malachi Harper poses as marshal just to impress his brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518180000 +0000" stop="20240518190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Saddle Stiff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben is challenged by a former employee to get himself hired elsewhere as a ranch hand, thus proving that his aging body can handle the intense physical labor of the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518190000 +0000" stop="20240518200000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Abilene</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When a possible smallpox outbreak gets the drovers quarantined in Abilene, Favor looks for a way to sneak out so he can seal a deal on a ranch. Meanwhile, an old foe of Rowdy wants revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518200000 +0000" stop="20240518203000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Treasure Trail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin wins part of a treasure map in a poker game and goes in search of the treasure with three other men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518203000 +0000" stop="20240518210000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>To The Victor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh is hired to convince the women of a town to come back to their men. The women left after making an ultimatum: give up your guns for good or we're gone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518210000 +0000" stop="20240518213000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Home Ranch</sub-title>
    <desc>"Two hired hands of a wealthy cattleman, who has been using the ranch for grazing his cattle, demand that Lucas move out. When Lucas refuses, he is beaten and dragged and then the ranch house is burned down."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518213000 +0000" stop="20240518220000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>End Of A Young Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is forced to give refuge to Will Fulton, a young bank robber who was injured while saving Mark's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240518220000 +0000" stop="20240519000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Healthy, Wealthy, Three Sappy People, Calling All Curs, Dizzy Doctors, Oily To Bed, Oily To Rise, Grips, Grunts And Groans, And Dumb</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Curly wins $50,000 the Stooges start living the high life? until they get the lowdown on exactly how much they get after taxes.
, The Stooges are phone repairmen who are mistaken for the psychiatrists in whose office they are working.  A rich man hires them to treat his impetuous young wife who is always running of for submarine rides and the like.  The boys ruin a dinner party at their client's mansion but their antics so amuse his wife the she is cured and the Stooges are paid off handsomely.
, Veternarians Moe, Curly and Larry find their business going to the dogs when one of their prize patients is stolen and held for ransom.
, Larry, Curly and Moe make a grand mess of things when they mistake the medicine they're selling for auto polish. 
, The Stooges are tramps looking for handouts.  Although the boys are down and out, Curly seems to get everything he wishes for.  After some trouble with a farmer, the boys come across an abandoned car, one of Curly's wishes.  The car actually belongs to some con men who have just gypped the widow Jenkins out of her land.  The boys wind up at the Mrs. Jenkins house just in time for a free meal.  To repay Mrs. Jenkins the boys try to fix her well and instead unleash an oil geyser.  Learning that Mrs. Jenkins has been swindled, the boys go to retrieve the deed before it can be recorded.  They find the bad guys and after a wild fight recover the deed.  The boys return the deed to Mrs. Jenkins and marry her daughters; April, May and June.
, The Stooges become trainers of "Bustoff", a champion wrestler.  The big boss has a lot of money bet on Bustoff and orders the boys to take good care of him.  Instead they accidentally knock him out and Curly must disguises himself as Bustoff and wrestle in his place.  The match doesn't go very well until Curly smells "Wild Hyacinth" perfume on a lady fan at ringside.  This drives him crazy and he knocks out his opponent and half the people in the stadium.
"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519000000 +0000" stop="20240519023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Scream, Blacula, Scream</sub-title>
    <desc>"Blacula, back in the world of the living by means of voodoo, is now loose with an insatiable bloodlust on a small community in the Louisiana backcountry."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519023000 +0000" stop="20240519030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Catwoman Goes To College</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E49</episode-num>
    <desc>Catwoman has a new parole officer: Bruce Wayne. Meanwhile, she plots to create a Batsuit of her own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519030000 +0000" stop="20240519040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Apple</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Primitive inhabitants of Gamma Trianguli VI worship a god who orders them to kill visitors from the Enterprise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519040000 +0000" stop="20240519050000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Chopper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Bent on revenge, a headless motorcycle rider murders those who wronged him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519050000 +0000" stop="20240519060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Forbidden World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On their next planetary stop, the Robinsons encounter a hermit who plans to attack the Jupiter 2 with his army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519060000 +0000" stop="20240519070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Man-beast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Crane, making experimental descents in the diving bell, turns into a beast-like creature threatening all on board the Seaview.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519070000 +0000" stop="20240519080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Target: Earth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Two giant scientists convince Mark to help them develop a spaceship so they can return the Spindrift crew to Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519080000 +0000" stop="20240519090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Alamo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1836, the travelers find themselves trapped with the defenders of the Alamo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519090000 +0000" stop="20240519100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Doomsday Minus One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A teacher stumbles upon a device that threatens mankind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519100000 +0000" stop="20240519110000 +0000">
    <title>Thunderbirds</title>
    <sub-title>Path Of Destruction</sub-title>
    <desc>"A tree-logging machine is out of control in South America and it's about as easy to stop it as it is to win a guerrilla war. Can International Rescue stop the thing before it reaches a dam construction site?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519110000 +0000" stop="20240519113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Glee Club   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang joins the Glee Club, but soon the friends lose their pep. Jesse catches Lisa's cold, Screech makes a fool of himself in front of his girlfriend's parents and the gang's singing is totally off key.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519113000 +0000" stop="20240519120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking Up Is Hard To Undo   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>First, it's splitsville for Zack and Kelly when Kelly goes on a date with her ex-boyfriend. Slater and Jessie are finally a couple, but things get messed up when they disagree on how to celebrate their coupledom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519120000 +0000" stop="20240519123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Video Yearbook   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack and the gang decide to make a video yearbook for Bayside, but when Zack uses the opportunity to create the "Girls of Bayside Dating Service," his friends get him back big time!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519123000 +0000" stop="20240519130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Snow White And The Seven Dorks   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang puts together a hip-hop version of 'Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs,' and Zack and Jessie get caught in a serious situation when Lisa catches them rehearsing the final scene—the KISS!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519130000 +0000" stop="20240519133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Dance (part 1)   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Kelly gets a job working at The Max but may have to tell Zack it's over between them when she falls for her boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519133000 +0000" stop="20240519140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Aftermath (part 2)   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack seeks revenge after catching Kelly with Jeff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519140000 +0000" stop="20240519143000 +0000">
    <title>The Flintstones</title>
    <sub-title>Ladies' Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>To be admitted to the ball game for free on Ladies' Day, Fred masquerades as Barney's date.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519143000 +0000" stop="20240519150000 +0000">
    <title>The Flintstones</title>
    <sub-title>Nothing But The Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barney has a toothache, Fred decides to save money by pulling the tooth himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519150000 +0000" stop="20240519153000 +0000">
    <title>The Flintstones</title>
    <sub-title>High School Fred</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Wilma thinks Fred is about to be promoted when Mr. Slate sends Fred to school for two weeks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519153000 +0000" stop="20240519160000 +0000">
    <title>The Jetsons</title>
    <sub-title>Elroy's Mob</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Elroy brings home the wrong report card by mistake, angering his father, which causes Elroy to run away with Astro.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519160000 +0000" stop="20240519163000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Vote For Brady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg and Marcia rush home after school with the news that they're both running for student body president. The boys and girls each take sides and soon each one of them is accusing the other of sabotage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519163000 +0000" stop="20240519170000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Voice Of Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Carol is asked to sing at church on Christmas, but loses her voice just days before the event. A hopeful Cindy asks a department store Santa Claus to bring Carol's voice back in time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519170000 +0000" stop="20240519173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Becomes A Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While Beaver and Wally are fishing an abandoned canoe floats up and they responsibly return it to the owner, whose name had been carved in the paddle. However, after telling his friends the story, they adjust it to make it sound as if Beaver had saved a girl from drowning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519173000 +0000" stop="20240519180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally The Lifeguard</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally is all set to begin his job as a lifeguard but is let down when he learns that had been a mistake and he's not old enough to fill the position, so instead he is hired to sell candy and hot dogs."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519180000 +0000" stop="20240519183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Gorilla</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly and Jethro both want a gorilla to help out around the house, so Jed asks Drysdale to get them one. Drysdale hires a man dressed as a gorilla to scare the Clampetts, but it fails. They put their new gorilla, Herby, to work doing chores and dress him in old clothes. Mr. Kelly, the man in the gorilla suit, wants out of the deal and gives his suit to Drysdale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519183000 +0000" stop="20240519190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Come Back, Little Herby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After the Clampetts don’t have success with the gorilla they took out of the zoo, they decide to get Herby back. They contact Drysdale who tells Mr. Kelly, but he refuses to do it. Mr. Kelly tells Drysdale he’ll return on his own terms and has Drysdale buy him designer clothes and expensive food. Herby returns to the mansion and starts living the life of luxury, dancing and dining with Elly by the pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519190000 +0000" stop="20240519193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>They're Off And Running</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Howell wins all of the Skipper's possessions betting on turtle races.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519193000 +0000" stop="20240519200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Three To Get Ready</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>The Skipper insists a stone found by Gilligan will grant the finder three wishes before sundown.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519200000 +0000" stop="20240519203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Takes A Dive  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After slipping on a role of pennies at the bank, a shady lawyer convinces Mama that she is badly injured and needs to sue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519203000 +0000" stop="20240519210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Gets Goosed  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama's cousin gives the Harpers a live goose for Christmas dinner, Mama relives memories of her childhood while the rest of the family is horrified at the thought of killing their new pet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519210000 +0000" stop="20240519220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Good Time Girls / Iron Man / Soap Star</sub-title>
    <desc>Three college women are mistaken for prostitutes; a fitness expert suffers fainting spells during triathlon training; a soap-opera star's jealous friend "auditions" for a new part with the lecherous costar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519220000 +0000" stop="20240519223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Ill-gotten Gain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie is given a bike after bringing home a report card filled with straight As. He soon discovers that the high marks were a mistake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519223000 +0000" stop="20240519230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Props And Costumes- Mark Short</sub-title>
    <desc>"Screen used props &amp; costume expert Mark Short shares his own personal collection with Lisa today and James Azrael of the Horror and SciFi Prop Preservation Association is here to value Mark's collection.  James has brought a screen-used weapon that Mark has been looking for to offer in trade."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519230000 +0000" stop="20240519233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Comrade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. discover that Charles is living the "life of Riley," thanks to the attentions of his menially paid Korean servant, Comrade Park, a man of unusual skills. He has an important contribution to make—a native remedy for a seemingly insoluble medical problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240519233000 +0000" stop="20240520000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of Gas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Heavy casualties are arriving, creating severe problems for the M*A*S*H unit because they are nearly out of Pentothal. Mulcahy takes up a collection from everyone—including a case of wine from Charles' private supply—and he and Charles take the jeep to make a trade with the black marketers for Pentothal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520000000 +0000" stop="20240520003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle Of The Month</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Being her time of the month, Gloria is in a complete foul mood and gets into a big argument with Edith, lambasting her for letting Archie boss her around. Soon, Gloria gets into a big fight with Mike and decides to sleep on the couch, however, no one can sleep when Mike and Gloria's bickering keeps Archie and Edith up. Meanwhile, all of this puts a damper on Gloria's birthday celebration.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520003000 +0000" stop="20240520010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>We're Having A Heat Wave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A heat wave hits New York, putting all of the Bunkers in bad moods and, to put salt on an already open wound, the air conditioner breaks down. When the house next door is put up for sale, Archie puts together a petition to prevent more minorities from moving into the neighborhood. Henry Jefferson hops on board when he discovers that a Hispanic family is looking at the home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520010000 +0000" stop="20240520013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>We're Still Having A Heat Wave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The new neighbors, Irene and Frank Lorenzo, settle into the house next door. Soon Archie is annoyed with both of them, as Irene makes friends with Edith and Archie soon grows jealous of all the time that Edith is spending with her. Meanwhile, Archie also becomes annoyed with Frank, whose constant singing filters into the Bunkers home prompting Archie to buy an air horn to combat the noise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520013000 +0000" stop="20240520020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith Finds An Old Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While shopping at the supermarket, Edith befriends a lonely old man, Mr. Quigley, who ran away from the nursing home. Edith swiftly brings him home with her and Archie is less than thrilled to have a constant reminder of his own advancing years hanging around the house. Meanwhile, Mr. Quigley has another problem when he can't get a hold of his uncaring daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520020000 +0000" stop="20240520023000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Washington Wacko / D.m.v., The / I'll Do The Talking</sub-title>
    <desc>In Washington Wacko, Carol goes bananas just before her husband meets the President. Then, in The D.M.V., Harvey's license plate gets mixed up with a confusing employee. Finally, in I'll Do the Talking, Carol and Tim talk to each other and over each other, oblivious to what they other is saying.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520023000 +0000" stop="20240520030000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mildred Fierce</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mildred Fierce, Carol and the gang parody the classic "Mildred Pierce", with Carol playing Joan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520030000 +0000" stop="20240520033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Happy Spangler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob returns a favor and hires an old friend and immediately regrets it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520033000 +0000" stop="20240520040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Never Name A Duck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob brings home two ducklings from the show, and Richie wants to keep them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520040000 +0000" stop="20240520043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Mind Your Own Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed sells irons after Ralph's advice got him fired from the sewer. When Ed lies about how much money he's making so that the Kramdens don't feel bad, Ralph considers selling irons, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520043000 +0000" stop="20240520050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Walking Distance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man decides to visit his hometown, he finds it exactly as it was when he was a child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520050000 +0000" stop="20240520060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Nothing Ever Happens In Linvale  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An eye-catching widow tries to convince an incredulous police officer that her neighbor murdered his partner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520060000 +0000" stop="20240520070000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>The Breaking Of The Habit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After fleeing a police roadblock where he gets shot in the leg, Kimble hops on a truck headed toward Sacramento where he meets Sister Veronica (the nun he drove from Nevada to Sacramento in the 'Angels Travel on Lonely Roads' episodes), who is now the pri</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520070000 +0000" stop="20240520080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Contenders: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Phelps and the IMF go after a crooked fight promoter who has gained a stranglehold over boxing and wants to extend the syndicate's influence into other sports worldwide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520080000 +0000" stop="20240520083000 +0000">
    <title>Peter Gunn</title>
    <sub-title>The Man With The Scar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy Davidson, the D.A.'s son, is being framed for a crime he didn't commit. Gunn investigates and is surprised by what he uncovers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520083000 +0000" stop="20240520090000 +0000">
    <title>Peter Gunn</title>
    <sub-title>Death House Testament</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ten minutes before his execution a convicted murderer hires Peter Gunn to find the $700,000 he stole, hand it over to the bond company, collect the 10% reward and give it to his daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520090000 +0000" stop="20240520093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Hired Killer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews races to save an innocent man from a murderous stranger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520093000 +0000" stop="20240520100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Clan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Friday is offered a bribe to assist a gypsy family trying to gain control of the gypsy community.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520100000 +0000" stop="20240520103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Little Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When a nine-month old child is beaten, Friday and Gannon investigate the parents, who are more concerned about their failing relationship than their baby son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520103000 +0000" stop="20240520110000 +0000">
    <title>My Three Sons</title>
    <sub-title>My Four Women</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Steve has major qualms when he learns what he is to wear on the runway at Barbara's women's club fashion show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520110000 +0000" stop="20240520120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill's Big Book Of Cartoon Facts</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill lands his first ever book deal... about facts, naturally."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520120000 +0000" stop="20240520123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Henry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>An animal is chewing up June's flower bed, so Ward and the boys set a trap to catch it. They soon catch a white rabbit, which Beaver talks Ward and June into keeping. Beaver names him Henry only to later discover Henry is really a Henrietta and she's expecting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520123000 +0000" stop="20240520130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Runs Away</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry gets Beaver into trouble when he goads him into trying out Ward's drill. Discovering that the boys damaged the garage wall, Ward hits the roof and scolds Beaver, who in turn decides to run away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520130000 +0000" stop="20240520140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lover's Gamble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An art critic is found dead in his bedridden wife's bed, yet his wife is nowhere to be found. The woman's caretaker is charged with murder, and it's up to Mason to find the truth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520140000 +0000" stop="20240520150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The D.j.  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When radio disk jockey, and Michelle's new boyfriend, Arthur Saxon is accused of murdering a rival, Matlock agrees to defend him. Michelle swears he's the kindest, most gentle man she's ever known, but Matlock soon learns otherwise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520150000 +0000" stop="20240520160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Small War: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Big city crack dealers invade Sparta. Eugene witnesses the drive by shooting of a friend and his offer to help the police identify the shooters leaves Harriet frightened and angry at Bill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520160000 +0000" stop="20240520170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Chicken Thief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A local "Robin Hood"" who steals from the ""haves"" and gives to the ""have-nots"" causes a crisis of conscience for John-Boy "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520170000 +0000" stop="20240520180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Pretender</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The Dano brothers return home from prison to a dying mother and a bitter father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520180000 +0000" stop="20240520190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Frenzy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The husband of Ben's friend, Anna Kosovo, suddenly becomes a raging lunatic, barricading himself and Anna inside their home, threatening to kill anyone who tries to intervene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520190000 +0000" stop="20240520193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Marshal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Micah Torrance, a once famous lawman, is introduced as a drunken derelict who stumbles into North Fork. Micah, nursing an arm crippled in a gunfight, is hired by Lucas to help out at the ranch. Three outlaws ride into town looking for revenge against Micah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520193000 +0000" stop="20240520200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Brother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark's uncle, Johnny Gibb, a big-time rodeo rider, comes to visit. While Mark idolizes his uncle, Lucas discovers that Johnny is on the run from the law for an Express Office robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520200000 +0000" stop="20240520210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Those Who Stay Behind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>"Hale is unable to take everybody on the next phase and has to turn down some of those applying. One is Ben Campbell, an ex-convict who is being hunted by his escaped former partner, who believes Ben turned him in to the law among others."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520210000 +0000" stop="20240520213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 54 -- Impersonation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed hope to find an impostor as they investigate a boxing promoter's accusation that a police detective stole $350 from him. In the meantime, they deal with a disgruntled wife who is in the process of destroying her own car in the middle of a downtown street, investigate a gun theft from a pawn shop, drive up on a home burglary in progress and obtain critical information while interrogating a suspected car thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520213000 +0000" stop="20240520220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 24 -- A Rare Occasion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy spends a weekend afternoon attending a barbecue at Reed's home, where Reed lets him hold his newborn son for the first time and tries to set him up with his wife's friend. However, their relaxation is interrupted when they have to deal with a young neighbor who overdoses on drugs and becomes the target of his dealer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520220000 +0000" stop="20240520223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>An Eye For A Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy takes being passed over for promotion philosophically until he hears of the rapid advancement made by a heroic helicopter pilot. Then his uncharacteristically bold actions stun Colonel Potter and the entire company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520223000 +0000" stop="20240520230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy writes a pre-Christmas letter to his sister, who is a nun. He recounts his frustrations at not being more effective at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520230000 +0000" stop="20240520233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>B.j. Papa San</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. almost becomes the surrogate father to a Korean family. Finding them a substitute for his own absent family, B.J. spends so much time with them that his medical efficiency begins to suffer, and Hawkeye worries about his health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240520233000 +0000" stop="20240521000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Inga</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>It's instant attraction for Hawkeye when a beautiful Swedish doctor, called Inga, arrives to observe combat surgery. That is, until she upstages him in the operating room with a superior technique, and his ego is bruised.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521000000 +0000" stop="20240521003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Date For Gomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is asked by Andy and Barney to take Thelma Lou's cousin, Mary Grace Gossage, to the Chamber of Commerce dance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521003000 +0000" stop="20240521010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Up In Barney's Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After being kicked out of Mrs. Mendlebright's boardinghouse, Barney becomes suspicious of the man who takes his room.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521010000 +0000" stop="20240521013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Brewster's Honeymoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampett money keeps rolling in as more oil is discovered on their land. And Mr. Brewster is coming out to marry his fiancée, Edythe. Granny is planning to go back home to the hills, but Jed decides to put up the cabin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521013000 +0000" stop="20240521020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>A Day In The Life Of Oliver Wendell Holmes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The law office of Douglas and Williams is open for business, even though the sign has Oliver Mendell Douglas (later Oliver Wendell Wilkie Holmes) listed as a partner. Unqualified secretary Lisa destroys a office typewriter before having the new phone connected to a fire alarm "clanger". Later, to boost business, she advertises a grand opening special with free prizes and discount law services.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521020000 +0000" stop="20240521023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink Vs. The Gonculator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan leads Klink to believe a rabbit trap is a secret electronic device in order for Klink to bring an electronics expert, who wants to defect, to camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521023000 +0000" stop="20240521030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Rockets Or Romance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan becomes the partner of a beautiful underground agent when he and his men team up with the underground to destroy a guided missile battery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521030000 +0000" stop="20240521033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mother Of The Bride / Stradivarius / Perfect Crime, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mother of the Bride, Carol gives daughter Vicki last minute marriage advice. Then, in Stradivarius, Harvey desperately seeks a repairman for his violin. Finally, in The Perfect Crime, Carol is married to a billionaire who is the most boring man alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521033000 +0000" stop="20240521043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Roving River</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Working to settle a land dispute in the Manzana Valley, Mason soon finds himself defending his client against a murder charge when the key witness is blown up by a homemade bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521043500 +0000" stop="20240521050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Escape Clause</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A hypochondriac exchanges his soul for immortality and indestructibility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521050500 +0000" stop="20240521053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Coyote Moon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A man seeks revenge after being robbed by hitchhikers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521053500 +0000" stop="20240521060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>No Pain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A man destined to live in an iron lung learns that his wife has been unfaithful to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521060500 +0000" stop="20240521070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Enter Tami Okada</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When a courier is abducted while en route to the Japanese consulate, Mannix helps a Japanese investigator trying to find the man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521070500 +0000" stop="20240521080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Reformer</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is hired when a crusading newspaper editor is found near a dead body, while drunk and unconscious in a hotel room."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521080500 +0000" stop="20240521090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Run To Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty's friend dies of an alleged heart attack during his constitutional.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521090000 +0000" stop="20240521093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Hostage Copter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews uses the Highway Patrol helicopter to rescue  a terror-stricken girl from abductors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521093000 +0000" stop="20240521100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Squeeze</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con accused of extortion is interrogated. He calmly and smugly insists that he is innocent, but Friday and Gannon have a surprise for him: taped conversations and a voice analysis device.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521100000 +0000" stop="20240521103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Suicide Attempt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon learn that a young man has called his mother from Hollywood "to say goodbye." With the help of the man's sister, the two detectives trace the impending suicide to a hotel with more than 1,200 rooms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521103000 +0000" stop="20240521110000 +0000">
    <title>My Three Sons</title>
    <sub-title>The Bride Went Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Chip becomes violently ill after eating Polly's cooking. Distressed, she feels it would be better for her husband if she left him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521110000 +0000" stop="20240521120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill Toons It Out</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill attempts to indulge in some mindful relaxation techniques despite Toony's constant interruptions."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521120000 +0000" stop="20240521123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is all excited to have his friend, Larry Mondello, stay over for the weekend. However, things start off on the wrong foot when Beaver and Larry get into a fight, which ends with Beaver punching Larry in the stomach.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521123000 +0000" stop="20240521130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Cat Out Of The Bag</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>The neighbors are going away for the weekend and Beaver and Wally have been put in charge of taking care of their lawn and their cat, Puff Puff. When Eddie shows up with his dog, Wolf, chaos erupts and Wolf chases Puff Puff away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521130000 +0000" stop="20240521140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fatal Fetish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After a pin-prick to a voodoo doll seemingly results in a stab wound through the chest, Mason is called to determine a more down-to-Earth cause of death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521140000 +0000" stop="20240521150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Captain  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Police Officer Jim Shanley is found dead, Sergeant Jerry Reese is charged with the crime. Everyone thinks he's guilty, especially Shanley's partner. In defending Reese, Matlock begins to realize that an old cop buddy of his isn't the man he used to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521150000 +0000" stop="20240521160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Small War: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The police wage war against the big city drug dealers who have moved into Sparta. Eugene identifies the men who murdered his friend. And Bubba is teamed with and intrigued by a lady police lieutenant from Jackson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521160000 +0000" stop="20240521170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Prize</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>As the Waltons prepare their entries for the local fair, an old suitor of Olivia's visits</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521170000 +0000" stop="20240521180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>South Wind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A boy goes into hiding after witnessing his father's murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521180000 +0000" stop="20240521190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Customs Of The Country</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe and Hoss enter a new world when they arrive in Agua Santos, Mexico. Joe breaks a law by removing his hat in church and Hoss encounters more oddities when trying to gain his release.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521190000 +0000" stop="20240521193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Eight Hours To Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Judge Burton seeks "justice" against the hangman who hanged his son; the judge who sentenced his son; and Lucas, the man who caught his son. When Judge Burton discovers that Lucas has a son, he decides that the best way to serve justice is an eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth, a son for a son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521193000 +0000" stop="20240521200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Duel Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When an Italian count arrives in North Fork, his strange attire attracts the attention of Groder, a town bully. Groder, trying to have fun with this stranger, destroys some of the count's currency, mocks him and tries to humiliate him. Eventually the count challenges Groder to a duel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521200000 +0000" stop="20240521210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Nancy Styles Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>"Spoiled Nancy Styles, claiming to be the daughter of the owner of the company that owns the wagon train, is determined to get to Denver by forcing her way onto it and then Hale makes it clear he plans to bypass the city due to early snow."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521210000 +0000" stop="20240521213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 124 -- Airport</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are rendered powerless when a drunken man with no flight experience decides to take a solo flight in a stolen airplane at a busy airport. Later, they try to locate a 17-year-old runaway living in a condemned home with a much older man, engage in a shootout with a convenience store robber and search for a booby-trapped bank safe that has been stolen with a tow truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521213000 +0000" stop="20240521220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 94 -- Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy fears that a boxer who has just been paroled after serving a murder sentence is going to seek revenge against him. Out on patrol, they try to save a man who has been crushed while working under a stolen car, apprehend a liquor store robber who swears revenge against reed, change a flat tire on their patrol car, locate a four-year-old child who locked himself in a refrigerator and become the targets of an ambush.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521220000 +0000" stop="20240521223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is confronted by two crises: Colonel Potter's mare, Sophie, mysteriously disappears from her corral, and Hawkeye and B.J. find themselves with a young Korean boy on their hands, who is trying to avoid conscription into the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521223000 +0000" stop="20240521230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Young And The Restless</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lecture on the latest techniques by a young surgeon from Tokyo, and a later demonstration of his surgical skill, turns Winchester into a drunk and Potter into an invalid, whilst bringing home to Hawkeye and B.J. that they are out of touch with new medical practices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521230000 +0000" stop="20240521233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips Is Back In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar, who is smitten with the cute new nurse, Linda Nugent, relies on Hawkeye's expertise on how to cope with the situation. Hot Lips, meanwhile, celebrates her just-granted divorce by taking a step that arouses Colonel Potter's ire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240521233000 +0000" stop="20240522000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>C*a*v*e</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th evacuation to a nearby cave to avoid US artillery fire on a Chinese target poses problems for Hawkeye, who has a claustrophobia problem of which Colonel Potter is not aware.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522000000 +0000" stop="20240522003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen's Arrest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gives Gomer a ticket for making an illegal U-turn, but then when Barney does it, Gomer has no choice but to make a citizen's arrest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522003000 +0000" stop="20240522010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And His Merry Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When Opie and his friends find a hungry man in the woods who tells them the story of Robin Hood, the boys begin to steal for the man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522010000 +0000" stop="20240522013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Frog Family</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny thinks Jethro has turned into a frog after he went swimming and takes him to Dr. Klinger in the bank building. Jethro stops by the bank and takes the frog home. Granny sees him at home and thinks he is cured. Jed decides to learn to be a frogman too, but when he tells Jethro, Granny jumps on him to stop him. Jethro takes Granny to her room, and Granny begs someone to end her suffering.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522013000 +0000" stop="20240522020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Economy Flight To Washington</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The Hooterville Young People's Agricultural Society, comprised of Eb, Hank and Arnold, flies to Washington, D. C. for the national convention. When the stewardess tries to throw the pig off the DC-3, the Douglases come on board to smooth over the problem. With Arnold hiding in "the occupied", the plane takes off with the whole Hooterville crowd aboard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522020000 +0000" stop="20240522023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Informer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Carter enters the camp and Hogan discovers a spy among his men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522023000 +0000" stop="20240522030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hold That Tiger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The POWs smuggle a tiger tank, about which Klink has been boasting, into camp in order to photograph and study it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522030000 +0000" stop="20240522033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Alan King</sub-title>
    <desc>In Sleep No More My Lady, Carol comes home from work, just as Tim gets up to leave, and the two must coordinate in their small apartment. Then, in The Reunion, Carol reunites with a high school friend and tries to convince her she's happy. Finally, in The Session, Carol visits a psychiatrist for the first time and meets a preoccupied analyst.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522033000 +0000" stop="20240522043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Shapely Shadow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Naive secretary Janice Wainwright carries out her boss' orders, placing a briefcase containing more than $100,000 in a train station locker. Then she waits for the arrival of his ex-wife but is met by an arrest warrant instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522043500 +0000" stop="20240522050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonely</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A convict serving time isolated on an asteroid receives a gift: a robot that looks, sounds and acts like a real woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522050500 +0000" stop="20240522053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Anniversary Gift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A man tries to murder his rich wife by giving her a poisonous snake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522053500 +0000" stop="20240522060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Dry Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A syndicate boss decides to test an ambitious young man to see if he's good enough to join him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522060500 +0000" stop="20240522070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Picture Of A Shadow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix finds himself drawn to a woman in a photograph—a murder victim. He sets out to bring her killer to justice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522070500 +0000" stop="20240522080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>House Of Cards</sub-title>
    <desc>"The accountant of Eden Corporation has disappeared and along with him three million dollars. Does unscrupulous branch manager Sheffield have to do with the plot? Cannon comes across a discovery and suddenly local reporter Julie Foster also plays an important role."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522080500 +0000" stop="20240522090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Price Of Anger, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A black cab driver runs from a murder scene on the grounds that circumstantial evidence - and racism - would make him the prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522090000 +0000" stop="20240522093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Rabies (christmas)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews desperately searches for a little girl who has been bitten by a rabid dog.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522093000 +0000" stop="20240522100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Departure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Petty theft from drug and hardware stores leads to a group of four teens who are determined to start their own nation on a remote island off the California coast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522100000 +0000" stop="20240522103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Investigation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are screening applicants for the Police Academy. One seems to have all the right qualifications, except that six months are missing from his application.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522103000 +0000" stop="20240522110000 +0000">
    <title>My Three Sons</title>
    <sub-title>The Power Of Suggestion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Against his classmate's better judgement, Ernie uses the unwitting Douglas household as Guinea pigs for an experiment assigned by his psychology teacher.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522110000 +0000" stop="20240522120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Animated Toys</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony take a look at animated TV series that were inspired by toys!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522120000 +0000" stop="20240522123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Poem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver comes to Ward for help on the night before a poetry assignment is due. This prompts Ward to totally take over the project and write the whole poem himself. Things get complicated when Beaver wins an award for the poem and Ward is faced with explaining the truth to Beaver's principal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522123000 +0000" stop="20240522130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A school dance has Eddie swooning over his so-called "girl," Caroline. However, it's obvious Eddie has made up their relationship when Wally and him visit her and she instantly becomes smitten with Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522130000 +0000" stop="20240522140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sad Sicilian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After a dispute between Sicilian business partners leads to murder, Mason is enlisted to find the culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522140000 +0000" stop="20240522150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Vendetta  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Michelle is taken hostage by Ned Billings, who blames Matlock for his brother's suicide after being convicted of murder, thanks to Matlock. Tyler and Julie end up as Ned's hostages, too, and the three try to use tactics they've seen Matlock use in courtrooms and interrogations to help them stay alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522150000 +0000" stop="20240522160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Frenzied Affair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Althea places herself in harm’s way trying to help one of her students, a disturbed and violent young man; after he is implicated in a murder case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522160000 +0000" stop="20240522170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Braggart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When a grownup Hobie Shanks visits the Waltons, John Boy seems to be the only one put off by his outlandish claims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522170000 +0000" stop="20240522180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Four convicts take Matt hostage on their way to Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522180000 +0000" stop="20240522190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Shanklin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When a rogue ex-Confederate soldier critically wounds Hoss in a robbery attempt, Ben learns that the very man who shot Hoss may be the only one in town able to perform a life-saving surgery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522190000 +0000" stop="20240522193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Safe Guard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Floyd Doniger comes to North Fork, looking to start a new life. He's got a steady job as the guard at the new bank and he's entertaining ideas of settling down on a spread of his own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522193000 +0000" stop="20240522200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Rebecca Snipe is returning to North Fork after a long visit away. Upon her arrival, Mark is smitten with her and gets it in his head to play matchmaker between her and his pa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522200000 +0000" stop="20240522210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Richard Bloodgood Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"A blind man called Sangre has joined the wagon train along with his guide. He is actually Coop's boyhood blood brother Richard Bloodgood, and he openly states his plan to kill Coop. Coop gets very hostile and refuses to discuss it whenever Charlie or Barnaby ask the reason Richard wants to kill him, but they know it has to do with the death of a beautiful woman long ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522210000 +0000" stop="20240522213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 104 -- The Bomb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a suspect who frames an employee of a manufacturing plant for theft and then plants a powerful bomb on the premises. They also apprehend two criminals after questioning a suspicious man who is carrying heavy bags down the street, and protect an innocent motorist from a street race that still ends in tragedy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522213000 +0000" stop="20240522220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 74 -- Light Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed spend a night shift on desk duty after Malloy breaks his wrist and another office worker calls in sick. With the assistance of a new female recruit, they deal with a homesick elderly woman who refuses to identify herself, help a lenient father bail out his son and become suspicious of a man who walks in looking for a wanted fugitive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522220000 +0000" stop="20240522223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rally Round The Flagg, Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The sinister Colonel Flagg pops up at the 4077th again, playing his usual spy games, convinced that Hawkeye is a communist sympathizer after he saves the life of a North Korean soldier. Also, an American soldier is less than impressed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522223000 +0000" stop="20240522230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Preventive Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On a sub-note, Klinger plays the part of a voodoo practitioner to try and get out of the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522230000 +0000" stop="20240522233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At Rosie's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A typical day in the life of Rosie's bar, complete with AWOL problem drinkers, a bound and gagged Winchester and a gambling scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240522233000 +0000" stop="20240523000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ain't Love Grand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The impossible happens for the snobbish Charles when he shares an emotional experience with Klinger, who discovers a US nurse, Debbie, finds him and his bizarre attire attractive, while Charles succumbs to the exotic charms of a Korean girl, called Sooni, who he meets at Rosie's Bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523000000 +0000" stop="20240523003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Cave Rescue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is the laughingstock of the town after he mistakes the owner of the Mayberry Bank as a robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523003000 +0000" stop="20240523010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie's Pal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy pays attention to a fatherless new boy in town, which makes Opie jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523010000 +0000" stop="20240523013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed And The Countess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>It is time for spring tonic, and the Countess Maria returns to meet with her good friends the Clampetts, as well as get some tonic. And after the Clampetts learn Maria is single again, having lost her husband at a party, Granny sees this as the time for Jed to make his move on the Countess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523013000 +0000" stop="20240523020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Retreat From Washington</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>With the Douglases in Washington, the "Haney Farm Mindin' Service" leases out their house (for $4 a day) to a couple with six children. Meanwhile in D.C., Lisa and Eb go to the White House to have unannounced lunch with the president, Kimball causes chaos for the Secretary of Agriculture, and Arnold causes problems in a laundromat. Oliver calls an early end to their trip, forcing Haney to quickly dispose of his new tenants.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523020000 +0000" stop="20240523023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Kommandant Of The Year</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Stalag 13 is named one of the top 10 prison camps in Germany, but it's just a distraction for Hogan and his men to destroy a secret rocket bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523023000 +0000" stop="20240523030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Inspector General</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A visiting general upsets plans to blow up a train.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523030000 +0000" stop="20240523033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Betty White</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Mama cleans out the attic, and Eunice finds out what happened to her childhood bunny. Then, in Counterfeit Bill, Carol tries to get rid of a fake twenty dollar bill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523033000 +0000" stop="20240523043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Captain's Coins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Historian Phillip Andrews argues that his fiancée, Evelyn Faraday, is entitled to a share of a shipping company fortune. Phillip then finds himself accused of murdering the company's top man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523043500 +0000" stop="20240523050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Time Enough At Last</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A bank teller pestered by the demands of his job and wife longs for time alone to read books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523050500 +0000" stop="20240523053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Blessington Method</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A unique society has a different method for preparing for the future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523053500 +0000" stop="20240523060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Weight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's plan to rid himself of a blackmailer backfires.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523060500 +0000" stop="20240523070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Desert Sun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mannix travels to New Mexico to prove that a Native American's death was murder, he runs into resistance from the townsfolk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523070500 +0000" stop="20240523080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Revenge</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is haunted by the memories of his time in the Korean War."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523080500 +0000" stop="20240523090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Killing Point, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby looks for a millionaire's mistress, unaware that she's stolen a priceless objet d'art.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240523090000 +0000" stop="20240523093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Hypo Bandit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews learns that a vicious bandit is on the loose with a "killer drug."</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
